（當你懷孕時，你該期待什麼）
Did you know that during pregnancy..
你知道懷孕的時候…
your fingers swell up to twice their size and never go back?
你的手指會腫成兩倍大 而且再也不會消了嗎？
Oh, my God! Let me see that.
天啊，讓我看看
You fall for it every time.
你每次都會上當
Hey! I brought you my old maternity clothes.
我把我的舊孕婦裝 拿來給你
Oh, Pheebs, that's so sweet. Oh, those are so cute!
菲比，那真的是太棒了 好可愛喔！
Look. See how they expand as the baby grows?
你看，寶寶越長越大 它們也會跟著撐開來
And after the baby's born they're great for shoplifting melons.
寶寶出生後 可以穿它去偷西瓜
Good, you're all here. Thanksgiving, 4:00.
太好了，你們都在 感恩節，明天四點
Guess who I invited? Remember Will Culvert from high school?
你猜我邀請了誰？ 還記得高中同學威爾卡佛特嗎？
-No. -He was in Ross' class.
-不 -他跟羅斯同班
Marching band, was kind of overweight. Really overweight.
他是儀仗隊的，有點胖 他是個大胖子
I was his thin friend.
我屬於他瘦朋友那一群
I don't remember. Are you talking about your imaginary boyfriend?
我不記得 你是說你假想的男朋友嗎？
No, that was Jared.
不，那是賈拉德
Wow. Haven't thought about him in a long time.
我好久 沒有想起他了
Will's here on business, and he didn't have a place to go, so I invited him here.
威爾來城裡出差，他沒地方可去 所以我邀請他過來
-That's nice. -Oh, he's lost a bunch of weight.
-那很好啊 -他減肥成功
He looks good. Okay, I mean really gorgeous.
他看起來很不錯 好吧，他真的是帥呆了
-I still love Chandler. -Wouldn't hurt you to say it once in a while.
-我還愛著錢德 -偶爾說一下不會要你命的
Just so you know, I'm not gonna make a turkey this year..
先說好了 今年我不煮火雞…
-What? -Phoebe doesn't eat turkey.
-什麼？ -菲比不吃火雞
-Phoebe! -Turkeys are beautiful, intelligent animals.
-菲比 -火雞是漂亮聰明的動物
No, they're not! They're ugly and stupid and delicious!
不是的 他們既丑又笨，也很好吃
Plus, eating them is like a tradition.
而且吃火雞是傳統
It goes back to the first Thanksgiving when the lndians sat down with the cowboys.
這得回溯至第一次過感恩節時 印第安人跟牛仔坐在一起
Oh, right. That's when they had that big rodeo at Plymouth Rock.
對，那個時候 他們在普利茅斯石辦牛仔表演
It's not just Phoebe. Will's still on a diet, Chandler doesn't eat Thanksgiving food..
不只是菲比，威爾還在節食 錢德不吃感恩節食物…
-Rachel's having her aversion to poultry. -She is?
-瑞秋對家禽類反胃 -是嗎？
Yeah. Remember? I had to leave the other day when you had that chicken.
對，記得嗎？ 那天你吃雞肉時我得走開
I thought that was because I put the whole thing..
我以為那是因為 我手裡…
on my hand and made it walk across the table.
拿著雞要他在桌上走的關係
It's not worth it to make a whole turkey for just three people. It's a lot of work.
為了三個人做一隻火雞太不划算了 那真的很費功夫
But you gotta have turkey on Thanksgiving!
但感恩節一定要吃火雞啊
Thanksgiving with no turkey is like Fourth of July with no apple pie.
感恩節不吃火雞 就像國慶日不吃蘋果派
Or Friday with no two pizzas.
或是星期五不吃兩個披薩
Fine, if it means that much to you. But there's gonna be a ton left over.
好吧，如果它真的對你很重要 但到時候一定會剩下很多
No. I promise I will finish that turkey.
不，我發誓我會把那只火雞吃完
You're telling me you can eat almost an entire turkey in one sitting?
你是說你可以一次 吃掉一整只火雞？
That's right. Because I'm a Tribbiani! This is what we do.
沒錯，因為我是崔比亞尼家的人 這是我們的專長
We may not be great thinkers or world leaders..
我們不是偉大的思想家 或世界領袖…
we don't read a lot or run fast, but damn it, we can eat!
我們書念的不多，跑不快 但該死，我們是大胃王
The One With The Rumour
本集播出：謠言
Four wide receivers. On third and 18.
第四次長傳，第三次18碼
Isn't it weird how next year there will be a baby at the table?
明年桌邊會坐一個寶寶 感覺真的很奇怪吧？
Rachel's. But good to know where you're at.
我是指瑞秋的孩子 但我很高興你還有在聽我說話
-Hey! -Hey!
-嘿 -嘿
-Happy Thanksgiving. -You too!
-感恩節快樂 -你也是
-Can I help? -Yes.
-需要我幫忙嗎？ -好啊
Chandler usually helps, but he's into the game.
通常錢德會幫忙 但他看球賽看得正入迷
Could you fold these napkins? I'm gonna go across the hall to check on the yams.
麻煩你幫忙折餐巾 我要去對面看看地瓜泥好了沒
No, sweetie. No, not like that.
不，甜心，不是那樣的
We're not at a barn dance.
我們不是在辦農場舞會
Fold them like swans. I showed you at Christmas. Remember?
把它們折成天鵝的形狀 我在耶誕節時教過你，記得嗎？
Yeah, it all just came screaming back to me.
記得，一切歷歷如新
-So how's the game? -I have no idea.
-球賽還好看嗎？ -我不知道
-What? -I'm pretending to watch..
-什麼？ -我假裝看球賽…
so I don't have to help out.
那樣子就不必幫忙
I don't believe you! That is brilliant!
我不敢相信 這招太高明了
-And Monica has no idea? -No.
-摩妮卡不知道？ -對
Once in a while, I just yell stuff at the TV.
偶爾 我會對著電視大叫
Hey! What? Aw! Hey!
嘿，什麼？啊
-Your team winning? -Anderson just scored again.
-你的球隊贏了嗎？ -安德森剛剛又得分了
There is no Anderson.
根本就沒有安德森這號人物
I wanna get in on this. Hey, Mon?
我也想如法炮製，摩妮卡
I can't help you after all. I didn't realize this game was on.
我真的沒辦法幫你 我不知道球賽打到哪裡了
-You like football? -Normally, I don't.
-你喜歡美式足球？ -通常我是不喜歡
But, you know, Green Bay is playing.
但今天是綠灣隊在比賽
-You like Green Bay? -It's only my favorite bay.
-你喜歡綠灣隊？ -那是我最喜歡的海灣
-Happy Thanksgiving. -Will, I'm so glad that you came.
-感恩節快樂 -威爾，我很高興你能來
You look great. You must've lost..
你看起來帥呆了，你一定減掉了…
150 pounds. I'll be on one of those Subway commercials.
150磅 我會是潛水艇三明治廣告的下一號人選
-A pie! -It's no fat, no sugar, no dairy.
-是派 -零脂肪，無糖，也沒有奶
-It's no good. Throw it out. -Meet some people.
-它不好吃，丟了它 -我來介紹你們認識
This is my husband, Chandler. This is Will.
他是我丈夫錢德 他是威爾
Oh, hey. I'd shake your hand but I'm really into the game.
我很想跟你握手 但我忙著看球賽
Plus, it'd be better for my ego if we didn't stand next to each other.
而且我們兩個只要不站在一起 就不會傷了我的自尊
-This is Phoebe. -Hi.
-她是菲比 -嗨
Hey. Wow!
嘿，哇
Well done.
做的好
-Wanna give me a hand? -I can't get over how great you look.
-你要幫我嗎？ -我真的覺得你很漂亮
-You look incredible too. You're so fit. -I'm watching the game, but I'm not deaf.
-你也很帥，你的身材真棒 -我在看球賽，但我沒聾
-I meant to tell you, Ross is coming. -Great, I love Ross.
-我一直想告訴你，羅斯也會來 -太棒了，我喜歡羅斯
Good. And Rachel Greene too.
很好，瑞秋葛林也會來
-Is there a problem? -No. It's okay.
-有問題嗎？ -沒有，沒關係的
It's just.. God, I hated her.
那只是…天啊，我恨她
-What? -I hated her.
-什麼？ -我恨她
She was horrible to me in high school.
高中時她對我很凶
But hey, that was a long time ago. I'm in a good place. Might be fun to see her again.
但那是很久以前的事了，現在我很好 或許再見到她會很有趣
Got any cakes or cookies or something?
你有蛋糕或餅乾嗎？
No, Will! No!
不，威爾
It's been a while since we screamed. Maybe we should.
我們很久沒大叫了 或許我們該大叫一下
-Oh, okay. No! -Come on!
-好吧，不！ -加油
Damn you, ref! You burn in hell!
該死的裁判，下地獄去吧！
What are you doing? You've got an entire turkey to eat.
你在做什麼？ 你還得吃掉一整只火雞
Let me explain to you how the human body works.
讓我跟你解釋一下 人體的運作方式
I have to warm up my stomach first.
我得先讓我的胃暖暖身
-Eating chips is like stretching. -Okay.
-吃薯片像是在做拉筋運動 -好吧
-Don't worry, Tribbianis never get full. -I'm here to tell you something.
-別擔心，崔比亞尼永遠吃不飽 -我要告訴你一件事
You can eat and eat, but nothing will ever fill that void.
你可以吃個不停 但你無法填滿內心的空虛
-Who the hell is this guy? -This is Will, from high school. This is Joey.
-這傢伙到底是誰？ -他是我們的高中同學威爾，他是喬伊
-Want some chips? -No.
-要來點薯片嗎？ -不
-Will! -Ross!
-威爾 -羅斯
Hey, you came! Man, you look incredible! Hot stuff!
你來了 天啊，你看起來棒極了，大帥哥
-Hot stuff? -It's good to see you, man.
-大帥哥？ -很高興能見到你
Yeah. You too. So, what are you up to?
我也是，你是做哪一行的？
-I'm a commodities broker. -That sounds interesting.
-我是期貨經紀人 -聽起來很有趣
-Yeah, it's not. -Oh.
-才怪 -喔
-But I'm rich and thin. -Oh.
-但我現在既有錢又苗條 -喔
I haven't seen you since Lance Davis' graduation party.
自從蘭西戴維斯的畢業派對之後 我就沒有見過你
That was such a fun night.
那一晚真的很瘋狂
Would've been good if we had gotten in, but still fun.
如果我們都有被邀請就好了 但那還是很瘋狂
We were lame. Do you remember how into dinosaurs we were?
那時我們遜呆了 你還記得我們多迷恐龍嗎？
-Yeah. -So, what do you do now?
-對 -你是做哪一行的？
So how long are you in town?
你要在城裡待多久？
-Hi. -Hey, sweetie. Oh, good.
-嗨 -嘿，甜心，太好了
Rachel Greene.
瑞秋葛林
Oh, that's right. Are you gonna be okay?
啊，對了 你沒事吧？
Oh, I'll be fine. It's just.. God, I hate her, Ross! I hate her!
我沒事，只是… 天啊，羅斯，我恨她
High school was a long time ago.
高中是很久以前的事了
Look at her standing there with those yams.
看看她拿著地瓜泥 站在那裡的樣子
My two greatest enemies: Rachel Greene and complex carbohydrates.
我的兩個死對頭 瑞秋葛林跟碳水化合物
Oh, my God. Who is that?
天啊，那是誰？
-That's Will, from high school. -Oh! I do not remember him.
-他是我們的高中同學威爾 -我不記得他了
Wow, really got that sexy smoldering thing going on.
他真的 越來越性感了
Oh, my God. Look at the way he's just staring at me.
天啊 看他盯著我瞧的樣子
He's trying to mouth something to me.
他用唇語跟我說話
I hate you!
我恨你
-Okay, dinner's ready! -Okay!
-好了，晚餐準備好了 -好吧
-Solid effort. Solid effort. -Oh, so who won?
-真的很精彩 -誰贏了？
-Green Bay. -Detroit.
-綠灣隊 -底特律隊
-What? -The Lions technically won.
-什麼？ -技術上來說獅隊贏了
But it was a moral victory for the Green Bay Mermen.
但在士氣方面 是綠灣美人魚隊贏了
Hi! Will, right? Right, hi. I'm Rachel Greene.
嗨，你是威爾吧？ 嗨，我是瑞秋葛林
-Oh, I remember you. -Really? Aren't you sweet?
-我記得你 -真的嗎？你真好
I gotta tell you, I'm having the hardest time placing you.
我得告訴你 我真的很難記得你的樣子
Hang on! I think I remember you.
等一下，我想我記得你
Did we fool around at Lance Davis' graduation party?
我們在蘭西戴維斯的畢業派對上 廝混過？
-You are unbelievable. -Thank you.
-你真是不可思議 -謝謝你
Rachel? Why don't you sit here? And Will, you sit way over there.
瑞秋，你坐這邊 威爾，你坐到那邊去
That's it? Even if nobody helps me, I can eat that. No problem.
就那樣？即使沒有人幫我 我也可以吃掉它，沒問題
-At least give me a challenge. -This is Chandler's chicken.
-至少給我一點挑戰 -這是錢德的雞肉
This is the turkey.
這才是火雞
Oh. How big is that?
那有多大呢？
-About 19 pounds. -It's like me when I was born.
-大約19磅 -它跟我剛出生時差不多大
-Who would like some yams? Will? -You'd like that, wouldn't you?
-誰想吃地瓜泥？威爾？ -你喜歡那樣做，對吧？
What? Oh, can we please keep the chicken..
什麼？ 拜託把雞肉…
and the turkey on the other side?
跟火雞放到另一邊去
-The smell is just.. -Typical.
-那個味道真的… -太典型了
-What? -I said it was typical.
-什麼？ -我說那太典型了
Typical of you. Queen Rachel does whatever she wants in Rachel-land.
你的典型作風，瑞秋女王 在瑞秋王國想做什麼就做什麼
Seriously, who is this guy?
說真的，這傢伙是誰？
Sorry, do you have a problem with me?
抱歉，你對我有問題嗎？
-I don't know. Do I? Do I? -I think you do.
-我不知道，我有嗎？ -我想你有
You were a little mean to him in high school.
你在高中時對他有點凶
-A little mean? You made my life miserable. -I had no idea. I'm sorry.
-有點凶？你讓我活在痛苦深淵 -我不知道，抱歉
Well, you should be. Screw it. Bring on the yams.
你應該抱歉的 去他的，把地瓜泥拿過來給我
But you worked so hard.
但你很努力在減肥
-Yams! -Okay.
-地瓜泥 -好的
I'm real sorry for whatever I did to you in high school.
不論在高中時我對你做了什麼 我都非常抱歉
It wasn't just me. We had a club.
不只是我，我們組了一個社團
-You had a club? -The "I Hate Rachel Greene Club"!
-你們組了一個社團？ -「我恨瑞秋葛林社」
So you all just joined together to hate me?
你們全都聚在一起恨我？
-Who else was in this club? -Me and Ross.
-還有誰加入那個社團？ -我跟羅斯
No need to point. She knows who Ross is.
你不必指我 她知道羅斯是誰
-You were in an "I Hate Rachel" club? -Yes, he was.
-你參加「我恨瑞秋社」？ -沒錯
No, no.
不
-So who else was in this club? -That exchange student from Thailand.
-還有誰參加了你們的社團？ -那個來自泰國的交換學生
But I don't think he knew what it was.
但我想他不知道那是怎麼一回事
You guys were cool.
你們太酷了
So, Ross, we went out for two years..
羅斯，我們交往了兩年…
and you never told me you were in an "I Hate Rachel Club"?
你沒有告訴我 你參加過「我恨瑞秋社」？
You went out with her? We had a pact.
你跟她交往過？我們說好的
-It's not like it was binding forever. -It had the word "eternity" in it.
-那不是永久的約定 -我們的確說了「永遠」
I'm thinking of joining an "I Hate Turkey Club."
我考慮要加入「我恨火雞社」
Although, I do love a turkey club.
雖然我喜歡吃火雞三明治
Monica? Did you know about this?
摩妮卡，你知道這件事嗎？
I didn't. Is that why you used to lock the bedroom door?
我不知道 所以你們才會常把房門鎖上嗎？
-Yeah. -A little relieved, I gotta say.
-對 -我得說我鬆了一口氣
Look, Rach, I'm sorry, okay? I was a stupid kid, okay?
聽著，瑞秋，我很抱歉，好嗎？ 那時我是個愚蠢的孩子
-The only reason I joined.. -Cofounded.
-我會加入社團是因為… -是一起成立
Cofounded.
一起成立
Cofounded the club, was that I was in love with you.
我會一起成立那個社團 因為我那時瘋狂地愛著你
I didn't handle it very well. If you think about it, the "I Hate Rachel Club"..
我處理的不好 如果你把「我恨瑞秋社」…
was really the "I Love Rachel Club."
想成「我愛瑞秋社」
Except that it was really the "I Hate Rachel Club."
但它真的是 「我恨瑞秋社」
So you'd get together and say mean things about me?
你們一起說我的壞話？
-We did a little more than that. -No, no, no.
-不只是那樣 -不
What else did you do?
你們還做了什麼？
-We started a rumor. -What rumor?
-我們散佈一個謠言 -什麼謠言？
Come on, Will, just take off your shirt and tell us.
快點，威爾 掙脫束縛告訴我們
-Ross? -It was no big deal.
-羅斯 -那真的沒什麼
We said that.. The rumor was that..
我們說…那個謠言是…
you had both male and female reproductive parts.
你同時有 男性跟女性的生殖器官
-What? -That's right. We said your parents..
-什麼？ -沒錯，我們說你爸媽…
flipped a coin, decided to raise you as a girl, but you still had a hint of a penis.
丟銅板決定把你當成女孩養大 但你還是有小雞雞
-Oh, my God! -You started that?
-天啊 -那是你們編的？
-You heard that? -Everyone at our school heard it!
-你也聽過？ -我們學校裡每個人都聽過
Everyone at my school heard it. You were the hermaphrodite cheerleader?
我的學校裡每個人都聽過 你就是那個雙性啦啦隊員？
Oh, no!
不
It makes sense now. This is why Adam Carter wouldn't go out with me.
現在我終於懂了 所以亞當卡特不想跟我約會
Why Billy would just stay in this region.
為什麼比利 只想停留在這一區
Billy's gay now, so that one's not really our fault.
比利成了男同志 所以那不是我們的錯
-Why didn't you tell me? -I thought it might be true.
-你為什麼不告訴我？ -我想或許那是真的
I was afraid that you were gonna cry and then show it to me.
我擔心你會大哭 把它掏出來給我看
Stop staring! There's nothing there! It's not true!
別看了，那裡面沒有東西 那不是真的
I'm afraid I'm gonna need proof.
恐怕我需要證據
Come on, whip it out.
快掏出來吧
You are my Everest.
你是我的聖母峰
-You don't have to finish. -I do. Otherwise, what's next?
-你不必吃完它 -我要，不然接下來是什麼？
Today I can't finish a turkey, but tomorrow I eat half a PowerBar..
今天我吃不完一隻火雞 明天我只能吃一半的三明治…
wrap it up and put it in the fridge? No!
把剩下的東西包起來 放在冰箱？不
I gotta change my pants. What was I thinking? Jeans have no give.
我得去換條褲子，我在想什麼？ 牛仔褲根本沒有伸縮性
Guys, help me with the dishes. There's a lot of pots and pans.
大家來幫我洗碗 要洗的鍋子真的很多
Honey, I'd love to, but the second game is about to start.
甜心，我很想 但第二場比賽快開始了
Oh, yeah, the second game. More football for the Pheebster.
對，第二場比賽 菲比隊要看足球賽
-Who's playing? -Los Angeles.
-哪一隊要比賽？ -洛杉磯隊
Last time I checked, Los Angeles didn't have a football team.
據我所知 洛杉磯沒有美式足球隊
Did I say Los Angeles? I meant the team that used to be in Los Angeles..
我說洛杉磯嗎？ 我是說以前在洛杉磯…
and is now in St. Louis. I actually knew that.
現在在聖路易斯隊的球隊 我真的知道這件事
Okay, quick, name three players on that team.
快說出 那只球隊的三個球員
Gretzky..
葛瑞斯基…
Agassi..
阿格西…
I'm a pretty little girl.
我是個小美女
Listen to what Sean McMahon wrote in my yearbook senior year.
你們看史恩麥馬洪 在我的紀念冊上寫了什麼
"Dear Rach, you're such a great person." Not girl, "person."
「親愛的瑞秋，你真是個好人」 我不是女孩，我是「人」
I think you're reading a little too much into it.
我想你太敏感了
"You're a great person. Sorry about your teeny weenie."
「你是個好人 關於你有小雞雞的事我很遺憾」
What do you want me to do..
你要我怎麼做？ 你要我…
call everyone in the entire school and tell them it wasn't true?
打電話給全校的人 告訴他們那不是真的？
-Yes. -Also, tell them I'm skinny now.
-對 -順便告訴他們我變瘦了
Oh! Me too!
還有我
I won't call anybody. It was a million years ago.
我不會打電話給任何人 那是很久以前的事了
I don't care. You told people that I was half and half!
我不在乎 你們告訴大家我是雙性人
I never did anything to hurt you in high school.
在高中時 我沒有做過任何傷害你的事
That's not totally true.
那不完全是真的
-What? -What?
-什麼？ -什麼？
You did start that rumor about Ross..
你告訴大家羅斯…
making out with Mrs. Altmann, our 50-year-old librarian.
跟50歲大的圖書館員 亞特曼太太親親抱抱
How did you know that?
你怎麼知道那個的？
-It's true? -No.
-那是真的？ -不
Yes, it is. I saw you guys going at it behind the card catalog.
不，那是真的，我看到你們 躲在書卡櫃的後面
-Hey, what were you doing in the library? -They had magazines.
-你在圖書館裡做什麼？ -圖書館裡有雜誌
Mrs. Altmann? She also made out..
亞特曼太太，她在…
with Ta-Taka-Ki-Kek the night before he went back to Thailand.
塔塔卡奇奇回泰國前一晚 也跟他耳鬢廝磨了一下
In high school you made out with a 50-year-old woman?
高中時 你跟50歲的女人耳鬢廝磨？
-Hey, she didn't look 50! -Did she look 16?
-她看起來不像50歲了 -她看起來像16歲嗎？
There's a picture of her in the yearbook actually.
事實上紀念冊裡 有她的照片
-Wow. -She didn't photograph well!
-哇 -她不太上相
She probably wasn't familiar with the process..
或者她不知道 該怎麼…
having spent most of her life sitting for oil paintings.
花時間 練習坐下來當油畫模特兒
How did this happen? Did she lure you to an early-bird dinner?
這是怎麼發生的？ 她一放學就請你吃晚餐引誘你？
I was working late in the library one afternoon. It was just the two of us.
有一天下午我在圖書館裡看書看得很晚 館裡只有我們兩個
She needed some help with her word jumble.
她需要人幫忙玩填字遊戲
And one thing led to another.
事情很自然就發生了
If you must know, Anita was very gentle and tender.
我得告訴你們 安妮塔非常仁慈溫柔
May she rest in peace.
希望她能得到安息
-Didn't she walk with a cane? -Only when it was damp!
-她不是柱著柺杖走路嗎？ -只有在天氣潮濕時
I can't believe you told people about this. Everybody knew?
我不相信你告訴大家這件事 大家都知道嗎？
-You know what? I'm back in the club! -Yeah!
-好了，我要重回社團 -耶
-Shall I call the meeting to order? -Is everybody present?
-我要召開大會嗎？ -大家都得來嗎？
With the exception of Ta-Taka.
只有塔塔卡沒有
-I wanna join! -Phoebe?
-我要加入 -菲比
I'm sorry, but I never got to be in a club. I didn't go to high school.
抱歉，我從來沒有加入過社團 我沒有念過高中
But three of us would meet behind a dumpster to learn French.
但我們三個 可以躲在垃圾箱後面學法文
Fine, you can have your stupid, little club.
好吧 你們可以繼續那個愚蠢的小社團
But what you did to me is way worse than what I did to you.
但你對我做的事 比我對你做的事更糟糕
-You gave me a teeny weenie. -Yeah!
-你說我有小雞雞 -對
You're just being silly. Rachel, even with that rumor..
你真的太傻了 瑞秋，即使有那個謠言…
you were one of the most popular girls. Everyone wanted to be like you.
你還是最受歡迎的女孩 大家都希望能跟你一樣
One girl wanted to be like you so much, she stuffed her pants with a Tootsie Roll.
有個女孩太想變得跟你一樣 她把棒條糖塞進褲檔裡
Wow.
哇
And Ross, if it weren't for her rumor, no one would've known who you were.
羅斯，要不是她的謠言 沒有人會知道你是誰
-She put you on the map. -As a romancer of the elderly.
-是她讓你成名 -以老女人的情人成名
Mrs. Altmann, you can tell, she used to be pretty.
可以看得出來亞特曼太太 她以前很漂亮
The eyes did still sparkle.
她的眼睛還是會發光
This stuff is so way in the past. You've been through so much since then.
這是很久以前的事了 你們也經歷過很多事
You got so much more important stuff going on in your life.
你們的未來 還有許多更重要的事
Can't you just let this go?
你們不能忘了這件事嗎？
-She's right. -We are having a baby together.
-她說的對 -我們的孩子快出生了
Hold on.
等一下
-You got her pregnant? -Yeah.
-你讓她懷孕了？ -對
-Are you getting married? -No.
-你們要結婚了？ -不
So you knocked her up but you're not gonna marry her. Dude.
你搞大她的肚子 但你不娶她，兄弟
-Anybody? -Okay.
-有人要嗎？ -好吧
It's exactly how I imagined it would be.
它跟我想像中完全一樣
All right, where's that turkey?
好吧，火雞在哪裡？
-Those are my maternity pants! -No, these are my Thanksgiving pants!
-那是我的孕婦褲 -不，這是我的感恩節褲
Well, that's it. I'm done.
好了，我吃完了
Here come the meat sweats.
留下了肉汗
Well, Joey, we're all very proud of you.
喬伊 我們非常以你為榮
I believe we can expect a call from the president any moment now.
我相信 總統隨時都會打電話來
-Anything we can do? -No. Just nobody press on my stomach.
-有什麼我們可以幫忙的嗎？ -不必了，但千萬別壓我的胃
You can keep those pants, by the way.
還有，那條褲子你不用還了
What you got there? What is that, pie?
那是什麼？ 那是派嗎？
-Yeah. You want some? -Just cut me a little sliver.
-對，你要吃一點嗎？ -切一小塊給我就行了
Little bigger.
大一點
再大一點
Are you afraid you're gonna run out? Cut me a real piece!
你害怕沒派吃嗎？ 切一大塊給我